lnt.com 2018-05-25

# 

This Policy was last updated on May 9, 2016.

## INTRODUCTION

The LNT website is operated and maintained by [One Stop], which is solely responsible for its management, your privacy and the website content. The Linens ‘N Things website is part of the Sequential Brand Group Family of Sites (“SBG Family”). Linens ‘N Things, LNT Brands LLC, Sequential Brands Group, and [One Stop] (collectively, the “Site,” “Linens ‘N Things” or “LNT.com”) respect the privacy of every individual who visits our websites or responds to our interactive communications. By visiting LNT.com, you are accepting the practices described in this policy. This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) outlines the information we collect when you visit the LNT.com website or respond to our interactive communications, and how we use that information. This Policy will also instruct you on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared when you visit the Linens ‘N Things Site or respond to our interactive communications.

The Data Owner of the Content for this Site is

SBG Family of Brands  
550 Continental Blvd  
El Segundo, CA 90245

The Data Controller for this Site is

One Stop (“Data Controller”),   
550 Continental Blvd  
El Segundo, CA 90245

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

_Voluntary Information_

You may visit and interact with the Linens ‘N Things Site without providing any personal information. Currently, Linens ‘N Things does not automatically collect what it considers personally identifiable information about you (your name, age, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) unless you provide that information to us voluntarily. For example, if you use the “contact us” section of the Site, we may ask for your name (or whatever identifier you would like to provide) and your email address. This is all the information we require to respond to your query. If you use our gift registry, we may ask you to create an account. If you want to have things sent to you, you may also choose to provide us with your postal address and information about where you shop. Except where necessary to provide you with a requested service, this information is not mandatory, however, and you will not be required to complete it in order to hear from an Linens ‘N Things representative. If you contact us through email communication, your email address and any relevant information contained in your email will also be collected. If you are not a U.S. resident, the information you provide will be used for the purpose for which you contacted us in the first place and deleted when it is no longer required.

We also collect information from other sources, including from social media and other websites associated with LNT.com. For example, if you are a U.S. resident and you post a comment on the Linens ‘N Things Facebook page or send us a tweet or message on Twitter, we may collect that information as described in this Policy. Please note that we may combine or cross-reference this information with other information that we collect about you and use it as described in this Policy.

In the event Linens ‘N Things conducts an online promotion, contest, or sweepstakes, we will collect certain personally identifiable information from your entry. If the promotion involves the collection of your mobile phone number, you will be provided a check-box at the promotion site to opt-in to receiving text messages pertaining to the promotion, and you do not have to provide your mobile number in order to be entered into the promotion or to receive any special discounts or other consideration.

_Automatically Collected Information_

We collect information that is not personally identifiable when you visit our Site. This includes the Internet browser you are using, general geolocation data saved on the device from which you access our Site (if you have enabled it), the computer operating system you are using, time spent visiting our websites, usage patterns within our websites, and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our Site or advertisement. It may also include aggregate information about our users, such as the number of users visiting the site or a portion of the site, all of which may be shared with third parties.

_Automatically Stored Information_

We may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “cookie” or similar file and will help us improve your experience on the Linens ‘N Things Site in many ways. A “cookie” is a small bit of digital information that tells us where you go within our site, and may also include information about where you have been on the Internet. Cookies allow us to tailor the Site and interactive advertisements to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser’s instructions or “help” screen to learn more about these functions. Note, however, that if you choose to erase cookies, your experience may not be optimized on this Site.

For EU users, we use cookies only for the sole purposes of carrying out the transmission of a communication to you, and for those purposes strictly necessary in order for us to provide the service you are requesting (such as fulfilling an order or answering a question).

_Making a Purchase_

The safety of your credit card information is important to us, and Linens ‘N Things makes commercially reasonable efforts to help protect the security of information you provide online in connection with a purchase.

As do many companies, Linens ‘N Things uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to help keep your online order information safe. SSL technology encrypts your credit card number, order information and personal information before it is transmitted to help protect it from being decoded by anyone other than us.

Most transactions are processed through Global Payments, Inc. Please review the privacy policy [here](https://www.globalpaymentsinc.com/en/us/privacy-statement) for more information on how Global Payments accesses your personal data.

If you choose to make a payment through PayPal, or Amazon, both of which are options for payment, you will be redirected to the Amazon or PayPal website and your information will be handled in accordance with the terms and privacy conditions you agreed to when you created your Amazon or PayPal account. If you choose to make a payment directly through the Linens ‘N Things, you will be using our trusted financial partners who use the SSL technology.

Making a purchase from the Linens ‘N Things site means, once you enter the checkout page, your computer will begin communicating with our server using SSL encryption. You can determine the security of your connection because the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https". If you are accessing our site from a browser or internet connection that does not allow SSL encryption. While we cannot guarantee that our security measures are 100% secure, we use this SSL technology to protect your information.

If you are accessing the site from outside the U.S., you may be connected to servers located within the United States or to servers whose privacy and data protection laws may not be equivalent to the laws in your country. When you provide this information to us, you are agreeing to the transfer of your personal information to servers and to facilities that may be outside of your country of residence and will be handled and processed in accordance with U.S. law. Once your order is complete, and there are no warranties or other reasons (such as to confirm the return of any product), if you are an EU resident, your information will be deleted from our servers or stored in a hashed manner that makes your personal information inaccessible.

We may work with third parties for international shipping purposes and you may be required to submit credit card and contact information to a third party to complete your order. Once you’ve completed your order, our third party shipping and processing partner will communicate with us about the status of your order, its approval status, and provide us with other information that may be relevant to the transaction. In many cases for international shipping, our trusted shipping partner must take title to the shipment and arrange for proper duties and taxes so that your order can be delivered to you. If you agree that information from your order may be shared with Linens ‘N Things, we will apply the same protection to your information as set forth in this policy.

## USE OF INFORMATION

If you do not want your personally identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to us. If you have already submitted this information and would like us to remove it from our records, please contact us at the postal or email address listed in this Policy and request removal. When you do provide us with personally identifiable information, we will use that information only as long as necessary to fulfill your order or other request with which you provided the information, maintain your account, or to improve the content of the Site. If you are a U.S. resident, we may also use the information you provide to notify you about updates to our websites, special offers, promotions, and/or to contact you for marketing purposes. Information we collect in connection with a promotion will be used consistent with the terms and conditions outlined in the promotion guidelines or rules, which may include a reference to this Policy.

Information we collect will not be shared for commercial purposes with other companies or organizations not affiliated either through corporate means or contract with Linens ‘N Things, or its brand group. However, in order to improve your customer experience, this information is shared with our SBG Family of websites and any third party service providers we use to maintain the sites or to process order information, all of which may be viewed here. In addition, we reserve the right to disclose or transfer any information we collect to third parties in connection with any proposed or actual purchase, sale, lease, merger, foreclosure, liquidation, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, transfer, conveyance or financing of all or any portion of the SBG Family or our affiliates.

We may hold on to personal information or release personal information if we believe in good faith: the law or legal process requires it; we have received a valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency; or such release is necessary to protect our rights, property, or safety, or that of our respective affiliates, business partners, customers, or others.

## REMOVAL OF INFORMATION

If you do not want your personally identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to us. If you have submitted personally identifiable information through LNT.com and would like that information deleted from our records, please contact us:

Upon receiving your request, we will delete your personal information from our existing files, as outlined herein.

LNT.com makes commercially reasonable efforts to comply with all state and federal laws, including CAN-SPAM. If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, you may opt out by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in the email you receive. You may also contact us at the postal and/or email address listed in this Policy and request that you not receive digital communications from Linens ‘N Things or its affiliated websites. We will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete your information from our active files, provided, however, that we may retain — for legal compliance purposes only — your request and associated email in a hashed format so that we do not inadvertently restore your information to our database. If you are a resident of the EU, you may be given the opportunity to opt-in to receive email communications. You may opt out at any time from receiving this information by following the instructions in any email you receive.

If you provided us with your mobile number, it will be used only for those actions for which you granted us permission, and you need only text “stop” in reply to any message you receive in order to opt out. Linens ‘N Things complies with the Telephone Communications Privacy Act, and will not contact you unless you have expressly opted in to receive messages from us.

## DATA CONTROLLER

The Data Controller processes the Data it collects from Users using appropriate commercially reasonable security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Data. The Data Controller also manages access to information collected on the site.

For this policy, the Data Controller controls the sharing of information you provide, and the Data Controller to process purchases in those countries where sales are made, for marketing and advertising purposes where allowed, for legal purposes (which may include providing access to User Data to law enforcement agencies, and for system administration, as described in this policy.

EU Users may request a list of third parties who have access to User Data upon reasonable request, by sending an email request to [email address]. In addition, we offer you choices about receiving interest-based ads from LNT or the SBG Family. You can choose not to receive interest-based ads from LNT by adjusting your advertising preferences by clicking the icon in the corner of the advertisement and opting out. If you choose to opt out of receiving interest-based ads, you will still see ads but they will not be personalized. User Data is stored on servers located in the US.

## FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

The California Online Privacy Protection Act requires that we outline our practice as it is related to federal do-not-track signals that may come from your browser. Because this signal does not often reflect the preference of our consumers, this website does not respond to it. Users may, however, request to unsubscribe, as discussed earlier in this Policy.

California residents may also request a record of all personally identifiable information we have on file, as well as a list of all third parties in the event Linens ‘N Things has disclosed personal information during the preceding year for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To obtain this information, please contact us at:

Onestop  
550 Continental Blvd  
El Segundo, CA 90245

Please include the phrase “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your email or on the envelope or post card and in the actual request. For all requests, please include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. We will not accept requests via the telephone or by facsimile. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.

## CHILDREN’S ACCESS

Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and its revisions in 2013, the Linens ‘N Things Site is a general audience website, intended for adult use. Linens ‘N Things does not market to, and does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from, children under thirteen (13) years of age. Please contact our customer service department if you are aware of any personal information supplied to the Site by a child under the age of thirteen (13).

To the extent any website that is part of the SBG Family of Sites does collect information from children, any children’s information is not shared with SBG’s general use websites, including this Linens ‘N Things Site.

## LINKS TO AND ACCESS TO OTHER SITES

From time to time, Linens ‘N Things may feature websites unaffiliated with it. Those sites may have their own privacy policies, or no privacy policies at all. You will be notified when you are being redirected to another site, and accessing these links takes you out of the Linens ‘N Things environment. Linens ‘N Things has no control over or responsibility for any unaffiliated third party sites or the content contained in them, and we provide these links solely for the convenience of our visitors. LNT.com does not sponsor, endorse, or otherwise recommend such sites or any products or services they may offer.

If you are linked to a site that is part of the SBG Family, please check the privacy policy on that site.
